lovdock.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy Policy

LovDock really respects your concerns about privacy and values the relationship we have with you, we respect and protect your privacy right as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use and protect it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By providing your personal information to LovDock, you are consenting to the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise manage that information. 

## Information Collection:

We believe it's important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site. We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, gender, age or birth date, zip code, country, IP address, browser information, social media name, your credit card number, credit card security code, expiration date, telephone number, billing address, and shipping address when you visit our website and purchase products on LovDock. We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue; never for marketing purposes. Our server stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. 

## The Use of Personal Information: 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To improve our website - we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  2. To improve customer service - your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  3. To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

## Cookies:

A “cookie” is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a website server that may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit our website, this site may store a “cookie” or similar file on your computer. This information may be used for general purposes such as providing you with more personalized service, storing your zip code, and even helping we track our website visits and traffic patterns.The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Remember, though, without cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our web site features.

## Information We Share:

We will not provide your personal information to third parties available for them to promote their products or services to you except the case of the third party seals and reseller we designated to sales. Without your permission, we do not sell or disclose the personal information of our website visitors in any ways.

## Children’s Privacy:

If you are under 13, you can visit our "Web site" but can’t provide your personal information to us. That is, you can’t register or purchase products on our website. Our website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. Once we get information you are under 13, we will remove it from the record.

## How to Protect Personal Information:

We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You may contact us at service@LovDock.com to request that we remove your information from our database.

## How do I Unsubscribe?

You can unsubscribe by using the link from any email newsletter or your personal subscribe setting after logged in LovDock.

## Privacy Policy Update:

We will revise this Privacy Policy to meet our honest LovDock fevers. If we change our privacy policy, we will update it here. Subscribe us to get the latest news.   
We restless try to ensure that your visit to our website smoothly and your privacy is always respected. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: service@lovdock.com
